Finding Aid for the Lou Hackett Silberman
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- University Career
  - Administrative Responsibi1ities (Box 29)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Physics Committee - Curriculum Vitae (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Physics Committee - Curriculum vitae (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Physics Committee - Curriculum Vitae (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Physics Committee - Curriculum Vitae (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Physics Committee - Curriculum Vitae (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Physics Committee - Memoranda (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Physics Committee - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Program Evaluation Materials, General (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Program Evaluations, Anatomy (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Administrative Responsibilities (Box 30)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations -Biochemistry (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Biology (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Chemical Engineering (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Chemistry (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Civil Engineering (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Comparative Literature (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Economics (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Economics (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Electrical Engineering (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Electrical Engineering (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - English (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Environmental & Water Resources Engineering (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - French & Italian (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Geology (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - German (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - History (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - History (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Mathemat ics (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Mechanical Engineering (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Mechanical Engineering (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Responsibilities (Box 31)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Mechanical Engineering (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Microbiology (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Molecular Biology (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Phiolosophy (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Philosophy (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Political Science (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Pharmacology (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Physics (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Physics (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Physiology (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Psychology (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Religion (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Religion (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Soc iology (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, Program Evaluations - Spanish/Portuguese (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Reports, Proposals, etc. (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Faculty Council - Reports, Proposals, etc. (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Graduate Fund - Jewish Students (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Grant 8, Fellowship Materials - ACLS, 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Grant 8. Fellowship Materials -ACLS, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Responsibilities (Box 32)
    - Grant & Fellowship Materials - Fulbright, 1956-1957 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Grant & Fellowship Materials - Fulbright, 1965-1966 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Grant & Fellowship Materials -University Research Council (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Grant & Fellowship Materials - Uanderbilt, 1951-1952 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Grant & Fellowship Materials, Others - Batey, Guenther (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Grant & Fellowship Materials, Others - Harrelson, Hauer (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Grant & Fellowship Materials, Others - Kaufman, Schachter, vanderbilt (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Humanities Committee (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Library - Judaica Collection (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Library - Miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Memoranda (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Memoranda (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Memoranda (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Memoranda (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Reports (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Navy Chaplain's Seminars (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Provost - Memoranda (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Provost - Memoranda (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Provost - Miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Provost - University Chaplain (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Publishers (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Senate Committee on Student Affairs - Meeting Minutes (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Senate Committee on Student Affairs - Memoranda (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Senate Committee on Student Affairs - Reports, etc. (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - University Rules & Regulations, etc. (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - University Committee on Faculty Responsibility (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Walburga von Raffler Engel (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Scholarly Associations and Meetings
  - American Academy of Religion (AAR) - Annual Meetings (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - AAR - Journal of the American Academy of Religion (JAAR) (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - AAR - Theolgy Committee (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - AAR - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - AAR - Paper Precis (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Association for Jewish Studies (AJS) - Annual Meetings, etc. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - AJS - Board of Directors Memoranda (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - AJS - Board of Directors, Minutes (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - AJS - Curriculum Development (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - AJS - Hebrew University Institute of Contemporary Jewry (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - AJS - Membership & Placement (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - AJS - Newsletter (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - AJS - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - American Society for the Study of Religion (ASSR) - Annual Business Meetings (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - ASSR - Annual Meetings (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - ASSR - Membership Lists, etc. (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - ASSR - Minutes of Executive Council (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - ASSR - Newsletters (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - ASSR - Newsletters (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - ASSR - Newsletters (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - ASSR - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - American Theological Society - Annual Meetings (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - American Theological Society - Membership Lists, etc. (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - American Theological Society - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Council on the Study of Religion (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Religious Studies Review (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Society of Biblical Literature (SBL) - Annual Meetings (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - SBL - Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - SBL - Publications (Journal of Biblical Literature etc.) (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - SBL - Seminars (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Studiorum Novi Testamenti Societas (SNTS ) - General Meet ings (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - SNTS - Membership (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - SNTS - Midrash Seminar (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - SNTS - Subscriptions (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - SNTS - Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - American Jewish Committee (AJC) - Fisk Consultation (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Atlanta Symposium of the Albert Schweitzer Centenary, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Biblical Studies Symposium - Carlton College, Oct. 25-27, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Colloquey on the Relationship Among the Gospels - Trinity Univ., May 26-29, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Colloquium on Jewish Studies - History & Perspectives, Brandeis, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Colloquium on Judaism & Christianity - Harvard Divinity School, Oct. 17-20, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Conference on the Jewish Religious Tradition -University of Chicago, April 17-20, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Judaism Colloquium - Brandeis, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Merton Festival, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Notre Dame Qumran Seminar, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Schleiermacher Consultation, Vanderbilt University, Feb. 28-March 2, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Summer Institute on Judaism & Contemporary Thought (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Tuohy Symposium - Jan. 8-17, 1973 2.5 vanderbilt Institute on Judaism (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Consulting
  - Canada Council (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc.; American Association of Theological Schools (ATS) - American Bapt ist (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Boston Theological Institute (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals - Center for Applied Research in the Apostolate (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Catholic University of America (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposlas, etc. - Center for Studies in Religious Education (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Claremont College (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Colgate-Rochester Divinity School (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Council of Southwestern Theological Schools (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Crozer Theological Seminary (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Dubuque Seminary (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Ecumenical Institute: Chicago (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc, - Eden Theological Seminary (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Esalen Institute (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Graduate Theological Union (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Havurat Shalom (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Institute of Religion (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Institute of Study for Christian Preachers (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Inst, for Theological Encounter with Science & Technology (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Nt1. Council of Churches (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Program for Inter-Professional Initiation (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Reconstructionist Rabbinical College (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Seminarians Organized for Racial Justice (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Twin Cities Seminarians (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Union Theological Seminary (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Univ. of Oklahoma (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Vanderbilt University (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Danforth Foundation: Grant Proposals, etc. - Yale University (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Danforth Foundation: Interview Records (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Danforth Foundation: Meeting Minutes & Agendas (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Danforth Foundation: Memoranda, etc. (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Danforth Foundation: Reports, Working Papers, etc. (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Danforth Foundation". Reports, Working Papers, etc. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Danforth Foundation: Reports, Working Papers, etc. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Danforth Foundation: Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Danforth Foundation: Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Religious Education Association (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - State University of New York (SUNY): Memoranda, etc. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - SUNY: Minutes, Agendas, etc. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - SUNY: Notes, Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - SUNY: Proposals, Working Papers, etc. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - SUNY: Proposals, Working Papers, etc. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - SUNY: Publications (Box 36, Folder 11)
    Book: Report: State University of Neui York Planning Committee for ReliQious Studies
    Book: Religious Studies in State University of Neui York
- Community Involvement
  - Community Improvement Association (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Goodwill Industries (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Metro Action Commission - Budget Material (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Metro Action Commission - Bylaws, etc. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Metro Action Commission - Meeting Minutes (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Metro Action Commission - Memoranda, etc. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Metro Action Commission - Office of Economic Opportunity Materials (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Metro Action Commission - Office of Economic Opportunity Materials (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Metro Action Commission - Proposals (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Metro Action Commission - Proposals (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Metro Action Commission - Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Nashville Community Relations Council (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Tennessee Commission for Human Development (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Tennessee Council on Human Relations - Memoranda, etc. (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Tennessee Council on Human Relations - Minutes, Reports, etc. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Tennessee Council on Human Relations - Newsletters (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Tennessee Council on Human Relations - Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Jewish Involvement
  - American Professors for Peace in the Middle East (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - B'nai B'rith - Anti Defamation League (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - B'nai B'rith - England (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - B'nai B'rith Hillel Chair - Vanderbilt University (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - B'nai B'rith Hillel Foundation - Institute for Race & Religion (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - B'nai B'rith Hillel Foundation - Summer Institute, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - B'nai B'rith Hillel Foundation - Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - B'nai B'rith Institute of Judaism, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Organization - Aleph Zadik Aleph Convention, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Organization - Girls Convention, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Organization - Summer Institute on Judaism; Materials on the Teaching of Judaism (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Organization - Summer Institute on Judaism; Materials on the Teaching fo Judaism (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Organization - Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Central Conference of American Rabbis - Annual Convention Materials (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Central Conference of American Rabbis - Commission on Jewish Theology (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Central Conference of American Rabbis - Committee on Unaffi1iated (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Central Conference of American Rabbis - Institute on Reform Jewish Theology (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Central Conference of American Rabbis - Newsletters (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Clippings - Magazines (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Clippings - Newspapers (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Council of Jewish Federations & Welfare Funds (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Hebrew Union College (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Havurat Shalom (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Havurat Shalom (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Institute for Jewish Life - Memoranda (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Institute for Jewish Life - Meeting Minutes, etc. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Institute for Jewish Life - Reports, etc. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Institute for Jewish Life - Reports, etc. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Jewish Life - Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Interreligious Dialogue: Catholic-Jewish Consultation (Nemi) (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Interreligious Dialogue: Chicago Summer Biblical Institutes (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Interreligious Dialogue: Jewish-Baptist Scholars Conference (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Interrel igious Dialogue: Memphis, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Interreligious Dialogue: Houston, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Interreligious Dialogue: World Council of Churches-International Jewish Committee on Interreligious Consultation Geneva Meeting (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Israel, State of (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Federation of Nashville & Middle Tennessee (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Jewish University Without Walls (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Welfare Fund (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Wolli Kaelter (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Nashville Area Jewish Community Council (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council - Gideon Bible Distributors (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council - Meeting Minutes, etc. (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council - Memoranda, etc. (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council - Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Printed Materials (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Zalman Schachter (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Sh'ma (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Norman Roth (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - United Assn. of Hebrew Congregations (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Zipporah Films (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Personal
  - Awards (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Children (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Clippings - Newspapers & Magazines (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum Vitae (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Financial - American Express (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Financial - Auto Europe (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Financial - Insurance (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Financial - Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Financial - University Salary (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Photographs (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Writings/Speeches By Others
  - ATS Presidential Address (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - ATS Papers (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Adams - Arent (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Baum (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Beck (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Bernstein - Blenkinsopp (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Borowitz (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Borowitz (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Bovon - Burghart (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Carpenter - Cox (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Crites - Crossan (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Curran (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Delorme - Ebeling (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Ebeling (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Ebeling (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Ebeling (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Ebeling (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Eckardt - Ellis (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Fackre - Fischel (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Forstman (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Francis (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Friedman (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Friedman - Friedrich (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Gadamer - Gaster (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Gershfield - Grech (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Harrelson - Heard (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Hendricks - Hendry (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Herzog - Hill (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Jenson (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Johann - Jones (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Kaufman (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Kimelman (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Konvitz - Kopald (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Lamm - Lelyveld (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Liskofsky (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - McGill (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - McKnight - Macquarrie (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Mansoor - Meyer (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Mims - Miskotte (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Neirynck - Nelson (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Neusner (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Neville (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Ogden (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Pannenberg (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Patte - Rengstorff (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Reynolds - Reuther (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Rivkin - Ryback (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Sabar - Sanders (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Schachter (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Schmidt (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Shemen (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Shemen (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Shemen (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Shinn (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Sibinga - Smith (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Spiegler - Stendahl (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Tal - Tanenbaum (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Thomas - Tolen (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Towner - Tracy (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Vogel (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Weinberg - Wilson (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Unidentified (Box 43, Folder 19)